{
    "id": "d1f0ff249f784dd9b9edcaa9c4a0d156",
    "title": "Formation of questions exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "1cdf19a9789d4bfeb8e723558518cc47",
            "title": "Formation of Questions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "........................... James play cricket?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Does",
                        "Do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................... Alice speak French?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Does",
                        "Do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................................... heat expand bodies?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Does",
                        "Do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Does Peter .................................... models from clay?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "makes",
                        "make"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Does she .................................... the violin each morning?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "practice",
                        "practices"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................................... they play well yesterday?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Does",
                        "Did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................... he go to office by train?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Does",
                        "Do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................................... the doctor coming to see her?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Is",
                        "Has",
                        "Does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................. the tablets bitter?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Were",
                        "Was",
                        "Have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Will our boys ........................................ the match?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "win",
                        "won"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................... Alice finished her homework?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Has",
                        "Have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Has he ............................... his exams well?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "do",
                        "done"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}